<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Speed Limit</string>

    <!-- EULA Strings -->
    <string name="eula_agreement">\n<b>License Agreement</b>

        \n\n<b>Speed Limit (“SOFTWARE”) End-User License (“LICENSE”)</b>

        \n\nAll copyrights to this SOFTWARE are exclusively owned by the author.

        \n\n<b>License</b>
        \nThe user is granted a revocable, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited license to download,
        install and use the SOFTWARE solely for the user’s personal, non-commercial
        purposes strictly in accordance with the terms of this agreement.

        \n\n<b>Restrictions</b>
        \nYou may not use, copy, emulate, clone, rent, lease, sell, modify, decompile, disassemble,
        otherwise reverse engineer, or transfer the licensed program, or any subset of the licensed program,
        except as provided for in this agreement. You shall not violate any applicable laws,
        rules or regulations in connection with your access or use of the SOFTWARE.
        Any such unauthorized use shall result in immediate and automatic termination of this LICENSE
        and may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution. All rights not expressly granted here are
        reserved by the author.

        \n\n<b>Limitations of Warranties and Liability</b>
        \nTHIS SOFTWARE IS DISTRIBUTED “AS IS.” NO WARRANTY OF ANY KIND IS EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED.
        YOU USE AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE AUTHOR WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR DATA LOSS, DAMAGES, LOSS OF PROFITS
        OR ANY OTHER KIND OF LOSS WHILE USING OR MISUSING THIS SOFTWARE.

        \n\nInstalling and using this SOFTWARE signifies acceptance of these terms and conditions of the LICENSE.

        \n\nIf you do not agree with the terms of this LICENSE you must remove the SOFTWARE from your storage devices and cease to use the product.

        \n\n(bbbadbudget@gmail.com)

    </string>

    <string name="eula_agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="eula_cancel">Cancel</string>

</resources>
